(Raj:)You two should be ashamed
of yourselves.
(Raj:)Using women to advance your cause
with sexuality...
(Raj:)...and whatever Amy plans on doing.
Are you implying my girlfriend...
(Sheldon:)...has no sexuality to exploit?
- Yes.
- Okay, because that wasn't clear.
- Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)What? That was ambiguous.
(Raj:)Well, now it's biguous.
What are you gonna do about it?
(Sheldon:)- Um...
- Talk some smack about his mother.
(Sheldon:)Yes, of course, he wouldn't like that at all.
(Sheldon:)Last night, I was feeling in need
of sexual release...
(Sheldon:)...when I happened to come across
your mother.
(Leonard:)- Okay, guys, what are we doing here?
- I don't know what you're doing...
(Sheldon:)...but I was about to insinuate that
I had coitus with Raj's mother for a dollar.
Well, you do what you want,
but I don't wanna lose my friends over tenure.
(Leonard:)- Friends are forever.
- Ahem. So is tenure.
(Bernadette:)Walk.